So once your lid has had a chance to set up and dry just a little bit, set it into your bottle and make sure that it fits nicely.
That's about just exactly what I wanted.
And then take, I'm not going to throw a knob, I'm just going to make a little hand-pinched knob.
So I'm just going to take a little bit of clay and roll it up.
And then just kind of pinch it with my fingers into a cone.
And that's a little bigger than I want, so I'm just going to cut a little bit of the base off there.
Now I'll take my scoring tool again, and score the top of the knob.
Score the top of the stopper, that is.
Score the bottom of the knob, and then just push it right on there.
And I'm going to smooth it in, all the way around, just gently with my finger.
And once you've got it on there, you can make it into whatever shape you want it to be.
You can carve, you can let it sit to leather hard, and then carve a form into it, if you want, or you can just make a little pointy knob, which is what I'm going to do.
And I'm pushing in here so that I have somewhere to grab.
So there we go.
It has a nice little organic looking knob.